Viewers all over the world, just as angels of God visited Paul and Silas,
they are on their way to you.
Viewers, listen. I mean it! Just as angels of God visited Paul and Silas in the prison,
right now, they are on their way to you.
I can't hear you!
Satan can only be defeated when you walk in Christ Jesus.
Right now, I repeat: Just as angels of God visited Paul and Silas in the prison yard,
right now, they are on their way to you - to heal you, deliver you, bless you!
Right now, begin to confess Christ Jesus! Mean it!
I say, the angels of God are on their way to you - to heal you, to deliver you.
Begin to receive!
This is the word from God - receive!
Healing to your soul, to your flesh! Be healed, be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Receive!
Receive, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, listen to me.
Because you are a child of God, satan has to listen.
Satan can only listen when we walk in Christ Jesus,
You are a child of God and you walk in Christ Jesus,
you talk in Christ Jesus, you look in Christ Jesus, you pray in Christ Jesus, you stand in Christ Jesus -
in Him you do all.
Satan, you must listen. I command you, in the name of Jesus, hear me.
You have to listen, in the name of Jesus.
I command you, right now, you satan -
I walk in Christ Jesus because I am a child of God -
I talk in Christ Jesus, I pray in Christ Jesus, I look in Christ Jesus.
Right now, you have to listen, in the name of Jesus!
Out of my life, out of my way, out of my career, out of my finances, out of my business,
out of my marital life, out of my family, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Rejoice!
The Word of God that said, "Let there be light" and there was light,
is saying, "Let there be light in your life, in your organs - let there be light!"
One thing you must recognise - darkness is sickness; infirmity is sickness.
Yes. Darkness stands for sickness. Infirmity stands for darkness.
Therefore, wherever these are in your system, let there be light, in the name of Jesus.
Receive light in your bones!
Receive light in your kidneys!
Receive light in your liver!
Receive light in your blood!
Receive light in your fluids!
Light, in Jesus Christ's name!
Rejoice!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
TT Monica Asefa
RV: Mel Flowers 10/02/2019